// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Select correct Uppercase letter 'a' ",
    answer: "A",
    options: [
      "B",
      "A",
      "C",
      "R"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Select correct Uppercase letter 'g' ",
    answer: "G",
    options: [
      "K",
      "H",
      "G"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Select correct Uppercase letter 'y' ",
    answer: "Y",
    options: [
      "V",
      "Y",
      "R",
      "A"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Select correct Uppercase letter 'q' ",
    answer: "Q",
    options: [
      "S",
      "L",
      "Q",
      "H"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Select correct Uppercase letter 'j' ",
    answer: "J",
    options: [
      "I",
      "S",
      "V",
      "J"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Select correct Uppercase letter 'd' ",
    answer: "D",
    options: [
      "Z",
      "B",
      "D",
      "T"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Select correct Uppercase letter 'n' ",
    answer: "N",
    options: [
      "M",
      "N",
      "X",
      "K"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Select correct Uppercase letter 'r' ",
    answer: "R",
    options: [
      "V",
      "R",
      "W",
      "A"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Select correct Uppercase letter 'h' ",
    answer: "H",
    options: [
      "A",
      "Y",
      "C",
      "H"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Select correct Uppercase letter 'v' ",
    answer: "V",
    options: [
      "V",
      "X",
      "A",
      "U"
    ]
  }
  
];
